[
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 1 = ?", "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "answer": "1", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 2 = ?", "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "answer": "2", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 3 = ?", "choices": ["2", "3", "4", "5"], "answer": "3", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 4 = ?", "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "answer": "4", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 5 = ?", "choices": ["4", "5", "6", "7"], "answer": "5", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 6 = ?", "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8"], "answer": "6", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 7 = ?", "choices": ["6", "7", "8", "9"], "answer": "7", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 8 = ?", "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10"], "answer": "8", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 9 = ?", "choices": ["8", "9", "10", "11"], "answer": "9", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 10 = ?", "choices": ["9", "10", "11", "12"], "answer": "10", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 11 = ?", "choices": ["10", "11", "12", "13"], "answer": "11", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "1 × 12 = ?", "choices": ["11", "12", "13", "14"], "answer": "12", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 1 = ?", "choices": ["1", "2", "3", "4"], "answer": "2", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 2 = ?", "choices": ["3", "4", "5", "6"], "answer": "4", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 3 = ?", "choices": ["5", "6", "7", "8"], "answer": "6", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 4 = ?", "choices": ["7", "8", "9", "10"], "answer": "8", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 5 = ?", "choices": ["9", "10", "11", "12"], "answer": "10", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 6 = ?", "choices": ["10", "11", "12", "13"], "answer": "12", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 7 = ?", "choices": ["13", "14", "15", "16"], "answer": "14", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 8 = ?", "choices": ["15", "16", "17", "18"], "answer": "16", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 9 = ?", "choices": ["17", "18", "19", "20"], "answer": "18", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 10 = ?", "choices": ["19", "20", "21", "22"], "answer": "20", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 11 = ?", "choices": ["20", "21", "22", "23"], "answer": "22", "time": 5},
  {"type": "multiple", "question": "2 × 12 = ?", "choices": ["22", "23", "24", "25"], "answer": "24", "time": 5}
]
